Conservative Party of New York State; Records apap060
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1962-1986; 7; 15 cubic ft.
  - City College, 1979 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 85)
  - City Council -- New York City, 1968; 1972; 1975-1978 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - City Council Districts -- New York City, 1974; 1976-1977; 1980-1981 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - City Fusion Party, 1972 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - City Planning Commission -- New York City, 1979 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - City University of New York, 1976; 1978 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Civic and Political Education Committee, 1973 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Civic and Political Education Committee, 1974 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Civil Court Act -- New York City, 1973 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Clarke, Joseph G., 1983 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Class Action Suits -- Legislation, 1979 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Clubs of the Conservative Party of New York State, 1979 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Cohalan, Peter F., 1982 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Cohn, Roy M., 1980 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Colleges, 1970-1972 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Colorado, 1964-1965; 1974-1975 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Colorado Conservative Union, 1981 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Columbia County, 1982; 1985 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Columbian Lawyers Association, 1975 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Columbus: Countdown 1992, 1986 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Combat, 1970-1972 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Committee for 76 of the Friends of Jim Buckley, 1975 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, 1962-1964 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Committee for the Protection of Family Life, 1975 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress, 1975; 1977-1979 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Committee of One Million (Against the Admission of Communist China to the United Nations), 1965-1966; 1971 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Committee of Ten Million, 1978; 1980-1981 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Committee on Political Education, 1963; 1967; 1971; 1976 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Committee on Public Safety -- New York, 1966 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Committee to Free Ken Duggan, ca. 1971 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Committee to Retire Jacob Javits, ca. 1980 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Committees -- New York Senate and Assembly, 1973 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Common Cause, 1972 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Common Situs Picketing, 1975; 1977 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Communism, 1963-1968; [1971]; 1975 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Community Alcohol Abuse Program, 1979 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Community Board No. 9 of Queens, 1979 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Community Colleges, 1976 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Community Development Amendment, 1971 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Competency Tutoring Program, 1978 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), 1979 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Comptroller of the State of New York, 1977 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Comptroller of NYS, 1978 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Comptroller of NYS, 1979 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Comptroller of NYS, 1980 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Comptroller of NYS, 1981; 3 folders (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 45-47)
  - Comptroller's Report, 1987 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Concordia University, 1976 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Condon-Waldin Act, 1966 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Con Edison, 1980 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Congo, 1962-1964 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Congress, 1967 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Congress, 1972 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Congress, 1974 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Congress, 1976 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Congress, 1978 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Congress, 1973-1974; 1988 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Congress -- Committee Employees, 1977 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Congress -- Legislation, 1975 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Congress -- United States, 1973-1980 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Congressional Bills, 1975 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Congressional Digest, 1963 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Congressional Districts -- 1st, 1972; 1976; 1979-1984 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Congressional Districts -- 2nd, 1975-1976 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Congressional Districts -- 3rd, 1972; 1974-1975; 1977-1978; 1981-1982 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - Congressional Districts -- 4th, 1976; 1978 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - Congressional Districts -- 5th, 1968; 1972; 1975-1976; 1978; 1980 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - Congressional Districts -- 6th (Folders 1-2 of 3), 1972-1982; 2 folders (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 70-71)
  - Congressional Districts -- 6th (Folder 3 of 3), 1972-1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Congressional Districts -- 7th, 1976 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Congressional Districts -- 8th, 1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Congressional Districts -- 9th, 1983 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Congressional Districts -- 10th, 1975-1976; 1978; 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Congressional Districts -- 11th, 1968; 1976-1978 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Congressional Districts -- 13th, 1972; 1978-1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Congressional Districts -- 14th, 1972; 1974; 1978; 1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Congressional Districts -- 15th, 1972; 1974-1978; 1980; 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Congressional Districts -- 16th, 1972 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Congressional Districts -- 17th, 1976-1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Congressional Districts -- 18th, 1972; 1977-1978 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Congressional Districts -- 20th, 1972; 1976; 1978 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Congressional Districts -- 20th, 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Congressional Districts -- 22nd, 1972; 1975; 1981 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Congressional Districts -- 23rd, 1968; 1972; 1974; 1976-1978 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Congressional Districts -- 24th, 1972; 1974-1975 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Congressional Districts -- 24th, 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Congressional Districts -- 25th, 1968; 1973-1974; 1976-1978 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Congressional Districts -- 26th, 1974-1977; 1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Congressional Districts -- 27th, 1968; 1970; 1974-1977; 1983-1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Congressional Districts -- 28th, 1974-1975 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Congressional Districts -- 29th, 1974; 1976; 1978-1979; 1983 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Congressional Districts -- 30th, 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Congressional Districts -- 31st, 1977; 1980-1982; 1988 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Congressional Districts -- 32nd, 1968; 1974; 1976-1977; 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Congressional Districts -- 33rd, 1972; 1974-1976; 1978; 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Congressional Districts -- 35th, 1974; 1976 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Congressional Districts -- 36th, 1972; 1974-1977 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Congressional Districts -- 37th, ca. 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Congressional Districts -- 38th, 1975-1976; 1978 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Congressional Districts -- 39th, 1968; 1976; 1978; 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Congressional Districts -- 109th, 1984-1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Congressional Districts -- Maps, ca. 1975 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Congressional Fund Raising, 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Congressional Monitor, 1975 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Congressional Pay Raises, 1977 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Congressional Quarterly, 1963; 1968; 1975-1976; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Congressional Record, 1961; 1971-1974 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Congressmen -- Ratings by Special Interest Groups, 1971 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Conklin, William, 1964; 1974-1976 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Connally, John, 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Connally Reservation, 1963-1964; 1971 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Connecticut, 1963; 1970-1971; 1973-1976; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Connecticut -- Correspondence, 1978; 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Conservation, 1963; 1966; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Conservatism, 1974; 1978-1981 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Conservative Book Club, 1964 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Conservative Campaign Committee, 1975 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Conservative Campaign Committees of Kings & Queens Counties -- News Releases, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Conservative Caucus, 1975-1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Conservative Digest, 1975-1976 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Conservative Digest, 1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Conservative Journal, 1974-1975 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Conservative Party of the United States, 1976 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Conservative Party Position for Information Please Almanac, 1971 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Conservative Viewpoint, 1975; 1977 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Conservative Voters'Guide, 1974 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Conservative Women of America, 1984; 1988 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Conservatives, 1976; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Conservatives for Duryea -- Campaign Coordinators, ca. 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Constitution Party of New York, 1976 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Constitutional Alliance, Inc., 1965-1967; 1969 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Constitutional Amendments -- New York State, 1971; 1975; 1977; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Constitutional Convention for a Balanced Federal Budget, ca. 1978 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Constitutional Party of Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Constructive Action, Inc., 1969; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - Consular Convention Between US & USSR, 1965; 1967 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - Consumer Affairs, 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - Consumer Alert, 1979-1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - Consumer Finance, 1976; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Container Laws, ca. 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Contras (Nicaragua), 1985-1986 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Cooper Church Amendment, 1970 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Copyright Law, 1964 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Correspondence -- Letters to the Editor, 1968; 1970 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Correspondence -- North Carolina, 1973; 1975-1977; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - Correspondence -- Oregon, 1973-1975 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - Council for National Policy, 1983 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - County Line -- GOP Publication, 1985-1986 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - Courts, 1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 82)
  - Courts -- Federal, 1973; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 83)
  - Crane, Phil, 1975; 1978-1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 84)
  - Crime Statistics -- Federal, 1973-1974 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 85)
  - Crime -- Violent Repeater Program, 1978 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 86)
  - Cromer, Jesse, 1975 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Cuba, 1962-1964 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Cuba, 1961-1965; 1975; 1979-1980; 4 folders (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3-6)
  - Czestochowa Shrine, 1974 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Cuomo, Gov. Mario, 1985-1986 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Dach Printing, 1972 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - D'Amato, Alfonse -- Folder 1, 1983 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - D'Amato, Alfonse -- Folder 2, 1980-1986 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - D'Amato, Armand, 1982 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Daemon College, 1981 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Death Penalty, 1978; 1982 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Decency Rally, 1969 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Defense, 1969-1970 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Delaware, 1971-1975 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Dellibovi (Assemblyman) for Congress Committee, ca. 1978 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1976 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Democrats, 1962; 1972; 1976; 1979-1980 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Demonstrations -- Student, 1968 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Deregulation -- Trucking, 1979 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Derounian, Steven B., 1963-1964 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - DeSalvio, Louis, 1975 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Detente, 1972; 1974-1976 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Dietl, Richard "Bo", 1986 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Dillon, Denis, 1979 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Dillon, Thomas J., 1968 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Dinner Journals -- East Side Conservative Club, 1977 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Dinner Journals -- Erie County Conservative Party, 1983 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Dinner Journals -- Kings & Queens Counties, Conservative Dinner Committees of, 1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Dinner Journals -- New York County, Conservative Party of -- Washington's Birthday Dinner, 1970 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Dinner Journals -- New York County, Conservative Party of -- Washington's Birthday Dinner, 1971 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Dinner Journals -- New York County, Conservative Party of -- Washington's Birthday Dinner, 1972 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Dinner Journals -- Onondaga County Committee of the Conservative Party, 1983 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Dinner Journals -- Westchester County, 1968 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Dinsmore, Herman H., ca. 1976 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - DioGuardi, Joe, 1985 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Direct Mail, 1980 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Disclosure Laws, 1980 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Discrimination, 1972; 1979 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Disenrollment of Conservative Party Members, 1979 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - District Attorney of the County of New York, 1974 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - District Attorneys, 1971; 1973; 1978 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - District of Columbia Amendment, 1978 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Division for Servicemen's Vote, 1963 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Dodd, Bella, ca. 1975 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Domestic Relations Law, 1979 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Doty, Charles R., 1983 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Douglas MacArthur Republican Club, 1970 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Draft, The, 1979-1981 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Droms, Fred W., Jr. -- Petition Against Secretary of State, 1968 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Drugs -- Head Shop, 1978 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Drug Legislation, 1979; 1987 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Drunk Driving, 1980 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Duggan, Kenneth J., 1966-1967 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Duryea, Perry, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Duryea, Perry -- Newsletters, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Dutchess County, 1983 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Dwyer, Terrence, 1977 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Eagle Forum, 1978-1981 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Eckert, Fred J., 1975; 1977 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Ecology, 1971-1973; 1976; 1978-1979 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Economics, 1968; 1973-1979 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Economy, 1979-1981 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Education, 1961-1969; 1971-1980; 2 folders (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 66-67)
  - Education, 1971; 1975-1981; 2 folders (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 68-69)
  - Education -- Federal Aid, 1961; 1963-1965; 1972; 1974 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - Education -- High School Competency Tests, 1981 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Education -- Higher Education, 1979-1980 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Education -- National Education Association, 1963; 1969; 1972; 1981 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Education -- New York State, 1970-1975; 1979 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Education -- Racial Quotas in College Admissions, 1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Education, U.S. Department of, 1979 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Edwards, Lee, ca. 1975 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - Eighteen Year Drinking Age, 1978 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1964 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Election, 1980 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Election Buttons, Undated (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Election Campaigns, 1980 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Election Cases, 1971; 1976-1977 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Election Fraud, 1980 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Election Law -- Folder 1, 1962-1969 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Election Law -- Folder 2, 1970-1979 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Election Law -- Folder 3, 1980-1982 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Elections -- Civic Organizations, 1964 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Elections -- Congressional and Presidential, 1964 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Elections -- Equal Time, 1964 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Elections -- Financial Reports, 1964 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Elections -- General, 1963 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Elections -- Gubernatorial, 1966 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Elections -- Gubernatorial, 1970 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Elections -- Gubernatorial, l973/74, 1978; 1980; 1982 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Elections -- Judicial Districts, 1964 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Elections -- Referendums (General), 1965; 1978 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Elections -- Voting Requirements, 1962-1963; 1966-1967 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Electoral College, 1977 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Electoral Reform, 1964; 1966; 1969; 1977 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Elwood Conservative Party Club, 1979 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - El Salvador, 1981 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Emery, James L., 1971; 1981-1982; 3 folders (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25-27)
  - Employees -- Public, 1968 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Employment, 1976 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Encyclopedia of Associations, 1979-1980 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Endangered Species Act, 1978 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Endorsement Letters for Candidates, 1974 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Energy -- Folder 1, 1977-1979 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Energy -- Folder 2, 1977-1981 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Energy -- Folder 3, 1979-1981 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - England, 1980-1981 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Enrollment in Political Parties -- by Assembly Districts, 1982 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Enrollment in Political Parties -- by Counties, 1982-1983 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Environment, 1975; 1978-1980; 1982 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Environmental Bond Issue, 1972; 1979 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Equal Rights Amendment -- Essay by Kevin McGovern, ca. 1978 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, ca. 1980 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Equal Time Broadcast Media, 1962-1967; 1974; 2 folders (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3-4)
  - Erie County, 1981-1982; 1985 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Erie County Conservative Party, 1970; 1983 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Espionage, 1964-1965 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Esposito, John A., 1973-1974; 1980-1981 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Esposito, John A. -- Busing Bills, 1979 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Estonian Aid, 1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Ethics, 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Ethnic, 1974-1975; 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Evans, M. Stanton, 1967; 1979 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Evans-Novak Political Report, 1974 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Evening News, The, 1974 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Exchange, The, 1976 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Family, 1980-1981 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Family Court, 1976 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Family Planning Public Affairs Office, 1976 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Family Rights Coalition (Abortion), ca. 1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Farber, Barry, 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Farber, Barry -- Campaign Finances, 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Farber, Barry -- Campaign for Mayor, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23-24)
  - Farber, Barry -- Campaign Fund Raising, 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Farber, Barry -- Campaign Literature, 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Farber, Barry -- Campaign Positions, 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Farber, Barry -- Petitions, 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Farley, Hugh T., 1980 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Faso, John J., 1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Federal Aid for New York City, 1974 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Federal Budget, 1979 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1964-1965; 1971; 1975-1980 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - F.B.I., 1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Federal Election Campaign Act, 1972; 1975-1976 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1974-1980 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Federal Employment, 1971 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Federal Finances, 1973; 1975; 1979-1980 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Federal Government, Power of, 1963; 1966-1967 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)